[
    {
        "front": "こめ",
        "back": "米 \nrice (raw)",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "おうべい",
        "back": "欧米 \nwestern countries",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "べいこく",
        "back": "米国 \nUSA",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "はくまい",
        "back": "白米 \npolished rice",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうり",
        "back": "料理 \ndish",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "しりょう",
        "back": "資料 \ndocuments",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうきん",
        "back": "料金 \nfee, charge",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ざいりょう",
        "back": "材料 \ningredients",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうり",
        "back": "料理 \ndish",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちり",
        "back": "地理 \ngeography",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "むり",
        "back": "む理 \nimpossible, excessive",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "りゆう",
        "back": "理由 \nreason",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "にく",
        "back": "肉 \nmeat",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "にくや",
        "back": "肉屋 \nmeat shop",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "とりにく",
        "back": "鶏肉 \nchicken",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶたにく",
        "back": "豚肉 \npork",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎゅうにく",
        "back": "牛肉 \nbeaf",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "きんにく",
        "back": "筋肉 \nmuscle",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "とり",
        "back": "鳥 \nbird",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "はくちょう",
        "back": "白鳥 \nswan",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ことり",
        "back": "小鳥 \nsmall bird, sparrow",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "のはら",
        "back": "野原 \nfields",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "やさい",
        "back": "野菜 \nvegetables",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "やちょう",
        "back": "野鳥 \nwild birds",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "やさい",
        "back": "野菜 \nvegetables",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "さいしょく",
        "back": "菜食 \nvegetarian",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "あおな",
        "back": "青菜 \nleafy green vegetables",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "おちゃ",
        "back": "お茶 \ntea",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "さどう",
        "back": "茶道 \ntea ceremony",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうちゃ",
        "back": "紅茶 \nblack tea",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゃいろ",
        "back": "茶色 \nbrown color",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "きっさてん",
        "back": "喫茶店 \ncoffee shop",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "めし",
        "back": "飯 \nfood",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごはん",
        "back": "ご飯 \nfood",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひるごはん",
        "back": "昼ご飯 \nmorning snacks",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "あじ",
        "back": "味 \ntaste",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅみ",
        "back": "趣味 \nhobby",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうみ",
        "back": "興味 \ninterests",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    },
    {
        "front": "いみ",
        "back": "意味 \nmeaning",
        "chapter": "N4 K14"
    }
]